写作技巧
    I broke into a sweat 
    My heart pounded, and my hand began to feel clammy against my bouncing knee.
    . I began to pace back and forth, stomping(跺脚）my feet impatiently at each end of the room.
   ·. The very act ofwatching was hurting my eyes, and my heart was still threatening to burst forth from my ribcage(胸腔）. 
    I wasso nervous I thought I wasgonna throw up again,
   . I couldfeelsweatbeading on myforehead as I walked around the corner. 
    My heart was in my mouth as I walked onto the stage.
    I couldfeel my heart in my throat as Tracy's blue Geo sliced through the eerie darkness of Martin'sstreet 
    