negative words that were oftenassociatedwiththecontinentinmediareports were the kind of terms her African classmates didnt want to hear.
    It's true that with incidents like the EbolaoutbreakinWesternAfrica andtheemergence ofpirates of the coast ofSomalia hitting the news,
   Whenitcomestothenatural environ  ent of Africa, our misunderstandin s are only bigger．   
    In her eyes, her classmates were as hopeful about the future of their own countries as they were about Africa as a whole, and they were quick to demonstr te both their strong will and initiative 
    (a more vibrant community with a shared future),
    团结振兴（unity and invigoration)
    少年强则国强(if the youth are strong, society will be strong),
    "你们青年人…-好像早晨八九点钟的太阳。希望寄托在你们身上(The young people ... are like the sun at eigh't or nine in the morning. Our hope is placed on you). ".
    be passionate about sth 酷爱......(=have a passion for sth)
    l've always been passionate about football.
    optional course选修课
    spare batteries备用电池
    stick in sb's mind 深深留在某人的脑海里
    lt's the kind of name that sticks in your mind.
    
    