I get goose bumps when I think ofsnakes.
    I was shaking like a leafafter seeing all those pictures.
    When she saw how steep the rollercoaster ride was, her heart was in her mouth.
     l break out in a cold sweat.
    She let out a scream ofpure terror.
    His eye brows shot up and he gasped,jumping backward instinctively.
    My fingers are curled into a fist and nails ate digging into my palm.
    I can feel the sweat drench my skin and the ringing screams vibrating in my ears.
    Fear overwhelms my body, making it exhausted.
    I wiped the sweat from my brow with a trembling hand.
    He slid down the door, bringing his knees up to his chest.
    
    live the life to the fullest.
    
    